{
    "id": "a84fab378fa94b9883f9b427705a4079",
    "title": "Adding contradictory remarks",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "112719c366a9464f9c6fc8d61b406673",
            "title": "Adding Contradictory Remarks",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He can speak English ........................... I can’t.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "But",
                        "And"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He won the test. ................................ his brother didn’t.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "But",
                        "And"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I like reading comics. .................................. my wife doesn’t.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "But",
                        "And"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ................................. me well but his wife doesn’t",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "knows",
                        "doesn't know"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "English is easy to learn but French ................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "isn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I did the homework but others .................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "did",
                        "didn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have learned classical music but my sister ...................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has",
                        "hasn't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "John .............................. but Peter hasn’t.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has arrived",
                        "hasn't arrived"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "James can sing well but Alice ............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "can",
                        "can't"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He will leave tomorrow  .................................... I won’t.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "and",
                        "but"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}